export const math_coaching_laws = [
    {
        choices: ["Mar. 8, 1998", "Feb. 12, 1998", "Jan. 28, 1998", "Feb. 3, 1998"],
        correctAnswer: "Jan. 28, 1998",
        question: "Republict Act 8495 &amp;amp;quot;Mechanical Engineering Act&amp;amp;quot; was a consolidation of House Bill No. 9806 and was finally passed by the House of the Representative on:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Law", "Subrogation", "Obligation", "Contract"],
        correctAnswer: "Contract",
        question: "It is the meeting of minds between two persons whereby one binds himself with respect to the other give something or to render some service.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["1894", "1793", "1973", "1739"],
        correctAnswer: "1793",
        question: "Republic Act 8495 &amp;amp;quot;Mechanical Engineering Act&amp;amp;quot; was a consolidation of Senate Bill No. ______",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Trademark", "Copyright", "Speciment", "Patent"],
        correctAnswer: "Trademark",
        question: "What refers to any word, name, symbol or device or any combination thereof adopted and used by a manufacturer or merchant to identify his goods and distinguish then from those manufactured or sold by others?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["novation", "subrogation", "obligation", "contract"],
        correctAnswer: "subrogation",
        question: "Which of the following is the transfer to a third person of all the rights appertaining to the creditor, including the right to proceed against guarantors, or possessors of mortgages subject to any legal provision or any modification that may be agreed upon.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Pre-existing Elements", "Natural Elements", "Essential Elements", "Accidental Elements"],
        correctAnswer: "Natural Elements",
        question: "Which of the following contract elements are presumed to exist.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Hero&amp;amp;#39;s Steam Engine", "Internal Combustion Engine", "External Combustion Engine", "Gear"],
        correctAnswer: "Hero&amp;amp;#39;s Steam Engine",
        question: "The official Seal of the Board of is represented by a drawing of:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Professional Mechanical", "Registered Mechanical Engineer", "All of these", "Certified Plant Mechanic"],
        correctAnswer: "All of these",
        question: "Which of the following can operate, tend or maintain, or be in-charge of the operation of any mechanical works, projects, or plants of 100 kW to 300 kW?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Republic Act 5336", "Republic Act 5455", "Republic Act 4567", "Republic Act 4356"],
        correctAnswer: "Republic Act 5336",
        question: "Which of the following is known to be the old Mechanical Engineering Law from which Republic Act 8495 is deduced from?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["30 days", "45 days", "20 days", "15 days"],
        correctAnswer: "15 days",
        question: "In R.A. 8495, Article 3, Sec 19, the reports of the examination ratings must be submitted by the board of examineers within how many days after the examination?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Transitory Clause", "Transitory Provision", "Effectivity Clause", "Repealing Clause"],
        correctAnswer: "Transitory Clause",
        question: "Section 47 of the Penal Concluding provision of R.A. 8495 is known to be the:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["per diem fee", "cost-plus-fee", "retainer fee", "lump-sum fee"],
        correctAnswer: "retainer fee",
        question: "What is the minimum amount paid by the client, usually total and in advance, for a normal amount of work expected during an agreed-upon period?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Effectivity Clause", "Qualifications of Applicants for Professional Mechanical Engineers", "Examination, Registration and Licensing of Registered Mechanical Engineers", "Creation and Composition of the Board of Mechanical Engineering"],
        correctAnswer: "Creation and Composition of the Board of Mechanical Engineering",
        question: "What is Article 2, Sec. 4 of Republic Act 8495?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["All of these", "Professional Engineer", "Certified Plant Mechanic", "Registered Mechanical Engineer"],
        correctAnswer: "Registered Mechanical Engineer",
        question: "Which of the following can operate, tend or maintain, or be in-charge of the operation of any mechanical works, projects, or plants above 100 kW, provided it is not more than 2000 kW?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Code", "Contract", "Canon", "Conduct"],
        correctAnswer: "Canon",
        question: "Which of the following is a fundamental belief that usually encompasses several rules?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Condonation", "Tenor of the Obligation", "Contravene", "Subrogation"],
        correctAnswer: "Condonation",
        question: "Which of the following is a gratuitous abandonment by the creditor of his right.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Alliance of Professional Organization", "Accredited Philippines Organization", "Allied Professional Organization", "Accredited Professional Organization"],
        correctAnswer: "Accredited Professional Organization",
        question: "What does APO means?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["PD 223", "PD 333", "PD 323", "PD 233"],
        correctAnswer: "PD 223",
        question: "What law created the Professional Regulations Commision?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Qualifications of Applicants for Professional Mechanical Engineer", "Issuance of Certificate of Registration and Professional License", "Scope of Examination", "Qualifications of Applicants for Mechanical Engineer"],
        correctAnswer: "Qualifications of Applicants for Mechanical Engineer",
        question: "Which of the following is Article 3, Sec 15 of RA 8495?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["PSME", "RME", "CPM", "ASME"],
        correctAnswer: "PSME",
        question: "What is the PRC&amp;amp;#39;s APO for the Mechanical Engineering?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Delegacion", "Novation", "Expromision", "Subrogation"],
        correctAnswer: "Delegacion",
        question: "What method of novation caused by the replacement of the old debtor by a new debtor, and which replacement has been agreed to by the said creditor to accept a third person to take his place as obligator.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["12 years", "7 years", "10 years", "5 years"],
        correctAnswer: "5 years",
        question: "One of the qualifications of Board of Examiners must be at least 35 years old and with a valid professional license and active practitioner for not less than how many years prior to his appointment?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["R.A. 2235", "R.A. 8829", "R.A. 8189", "R.A. 8981"],
        correctAnswer: "R.A. 8981",
        question: "What is the otherwise known as &amp;amp;quot;PRC Modernization Law&amp;amp;quot;?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["House of Representative", "Commission of Appointment", "President of the Republic", "Senate President"],
        correctAnswer: "President of the Republic",
        question: "The board of Mechanical Engineering is composed of Chairman and two (2) members duly appointed by the:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["063", "004", "010", "008"],
        correctAnswer: "010",
        question: "What is the PSME&amp;amp;#39;s PRC accreditation number?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Disreputation", "Fraud", "Conduct", "Tort"],
        correctAnswer: "Tort",
        question: "What is the civil wrong committed by one person causing damage to another person or person&amp;amp;#39;s property, emotional well-being or reputation?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["per diem fee", "lump-sum fee", "retainer fee", "cost-plus-fee"],
        correctAnswer: "per diem fee",
        question: "WHat is the specific sum for each day spent by an engineer (e.g., travel, production and etc)?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Delegacion", "Compensation", "Novation", "Subrogation"],
        correctAnswer: "Novation",
        question: "What term is used in the substitution or alternation of an obligation that cancels or modifies the one preceding it?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["5 terms", "2 terms", "3 terms", "4 terms"],
        correctAnswer: "2 terms",
        question: "For the term of office for Board of Examiners, no member of the Board shall hold office for a term more than how many regular terms?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["senior citizen", "demented citizen", "dead person", "minors"],
        correctAnswer: "demented citizen",
        question: "Which of the following parties whose consent or signature in a contract is not considered intelligent?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Delay", "Negligence", "Negligence", "Fraud"],
        correctAnswer: "Delay",
        question: "Which of the following is the failure to perform an obligation on time except when it is caused by a fortuitous event.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["RME", "PAMEE", "PSME", "IIEE"],
        correctAnswer: "PSME",
        question: "What is the National Association for Mechanical Engineers accredited by the Professional Regulation Commission?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Repealing Clause", "Transitory Provision", "Effectivity Clause", "Transitory Clause"],
        correctAnswer: "Repealing Clause",
        question: "Section 46 of the Penal and Concluding provision of R.A. 8495 is known to be the:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Sec. 40", "Sec. 38", "Sec. 39", "Sec. 48"],
        correctAnswer: "Sec. 39",
        question: "Which of the following sections of Republic Act 8495 deals on Foreign Reciprocity of the Foreign Mechanical Engineers?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Obligation", "Conduct", "Law", "Subrogation"],
        correctAnswer: "Obligation",
        question: "Which of the following is a juridical relation whereby a person may demand from another, the observance of a determinate conduct and in case of breach may demand the satisfaction from the assets of the latter.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Cost-Plus-Fee", "Per Diem Fee", "Salary Plus", "Lump-sum Fee"],
        correctAnswer: "Lump-sum Fee",
        question: "Which of the following is a predetermined fee agreed upon by client usually for small projects where the scope of work is clearly defined?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["four (4)", "six (6)", "five (5)", "three (3)"],
        correctAnswer: "three (3)",
        question: "The Board of Mechanical Engineering is composed of Chairman and two (2) members duly appointed by the Republic from a list of how many recomendees for each position?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["PME", "RME", "CPM", "IIEE"],
        correctAnswer: "PME",
        question: "What is the minimum grade of Mechanical Engineer required in the design and preparation of plans of 280 KW diesel power plant?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Transitory Provision", "Effectivity Clause", "Separability Clause", "Repealing Clause"],
        correctAnswer: "Separability Clause",
        question: "Section 45 of the Penal Concluding provision of R.A. 8495 is known to be the:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Conceptions", "Perfection of Birth", "Termination", "Consummation"],
        correctAnswer: "Conceptions",
        question: "Which of the following stages of contracts that includes all the negotaitons or steps taken by the parties leading to its perfection.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["10 years", "3 years", "4 years", "5 years"],
        correctAnswer: "5 years",
        question: "What is the minimum number of years active in mechanical engineering practice for an RME to be qualified applicant for PME is required?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["9806", "1793", "1739", "1973"],
        correctAnswer: "9806",
        question: "Republic Act 8495 &amp;amp;quot;Mechanical Engineering Act&amp;amp;quot; was a consilidation of House Bill No. _________.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["2 members", "4 members", "3 members", "5 members"],
        correctAnswer: "2 members",
        question: "The Board of Mechanical Engineering is composed of a Chairman and:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Conduct", "Code", "Rule", "Canon"],
        correctAnswer: "Rule",
        question: "Which of the following is a guide for conduct and action in a certain situation?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Negligence", "Non-compliance of CPE requirements", "Unprofessional or dishonorable Conduct", "Violations of Code of Ethics for ME and CPM"],
        correctAnswer: "Non-compliance of CPE requirements",
        question: "Which of the following cannot be anymore ground of suspension or Revocation of Certificates as Mechanical Engineer?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Board of Mechanical Engineering", "Practice of the Profession", "Examination, Registration and License", "Penal and Concluding Provisions"],
        correctAnswer: "Examination, Registration and License",
        question: "Which of the following is Article 3 of the Republic Act 8495?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Negligence", "Breach of Contract", "Material Breach", "Fraud"],
        correctAnswer: "Breach of Contract",
        question: "What is the term used when one of the parties fail to satisfy all of its obligation under contract?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["5", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswer: "5",
        question: "How many articles are there in Republic Act 8495?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["gears and sprocket", "cylindrical kettle mounted on a three-legged metal", "gear inside a cylindrical kettle", "cylindrical kettle inside a gear"],
        correctAnswer: "cylindrical kettle mounted on a three-legged metal",
        question: "The official Seal of the Board is represented by a drawing of Hero&amp;amp;#39;s Steam. First Century A.D. consisting of a:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Sec 2", "Sec 5", "Sec 3", "Sec 4"],
        correctAnswer: "Sec 2",
        question: "Which of the following sections in R.A. 8495 is the Statement of Policy?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["P 300,000.00", "P 200,000.00", "P 400,000.00", "P 150,000.00"],
        correctAnswer: "P 200,000.00",
        question: "Under the penalty provision of R.A. 8495, violations of such provision upon conviction be penalized by a fine of not less than fifty thousand pesos (P 50,000.00) not more than:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Franchise", "Corporation", "Partnership", "Legal agency"],
        correctAnswer: "Partnership",
        question: "What is the ownership by two or more persons?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Copyright", "Specification", "Models", "Trademark"],
        correctAnswer: "Specification",
        question: "What refers to a written description of the invention, and of the manner and process of making and using it, in such full, clear, concise and exat terms as to enable any person skilled in the art tow hich it pertains to make and use the same, and shall set forth the best modecontemplated by the inventor of carrying out his invention?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Conduct", "Contract", "Creed", "Code"],
        correctAnswer: "Code",
        question: "Which of the following is a system of non-statutory, non-mandatory canons of personal conduct?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Subrogation", "Acceptance", "Delegacion", "Expromision"],
        correctAnswer: "Expromision",
        question: "What method of novation when a third person of his own accord and even without the knowledge of the original debtor assumes tha obligation with the consent of the creditor?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Jan 28, 1989", "Feb 12, 1989", "Feb 3, 1989", "Mar 8, 1989"],
        correctAnswer: "Feb 3, 1989",
        question: "Republic Act 8495 &amp;amp;quot;Mechanical Engineering Act&amp;amp;quot; was a consolidation of Senate Bill No. 1793 and by the Senate on:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["20 days", "15 days", "20 days", "12 days"],
        correctAnswer: "15 days",
        question: "How many days does R.A. 8495 took effect following its publication in the Official Gazzete or a major daily newspaper of general circulation?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Unprofessional or dishonorable Conduct", "Violations of Code of Ethics for ME and CPM", "All of these ", "Negligence"],
        correctAnswer: "All of these ",
        question: "Which of the following can be a ground of suspension or Revocation of Certificates as Mechanical Engineer?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Repealing Clause", "Effectivity Clause", "Implementing Rules and Regulations", "Transitory Provision"],
        correctAnswer: "Implementing Rules and Regulations",
        question: "Section 43 of the Penal and Concluding provision of R.A. 8495 is known to be the:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["All of these", "Delay", "Negligence", "Fraud"],
        correctAnswer: "All of these",
        question: "Which of the following can be a ground for liability which may entitle the injured party to claim for damages?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Lump-Sum-Fee", "Cost Plus Fixed Fee", "Salary Plus", "Per Diem Fee"],
        correctAnswer: "Cost Plus Fixed Fee",
        question: "Which of the following is the total cost incurred by an engineer (e.g. labor, material, travel &amp;amp;amp; etc.)?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Delay", "Negligence", "Fraud", "Contravene"],
        correctAnswer: "Fraud",
        question: "Which of the following is an intentional evasion for the fulfillment of an obligation.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["All of these", "Registered Mechanical Engineer", "Certified Plant Mechanic", "Professional Engineer"],
        correctAnswer: "Professional Engineer",
        question: "Which of the following can operate, tend or maintain, or be in-charge of the operation of any mechanical works, projects, or plants of more than 2000 kW?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Gloria Macapagal Arroyo", "COrazon C. Aquino", "Fidel V. Ramos", "Joseph Ejercito Estrada"],
        correctAnswer: "Fidel V. Ramos",
        question: "Who was the president of the Republic that approved R.A. 8495?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Creed", "Conduct", "Contract", "Code"],
        correctAnswer: "Creed",
        question: "Which of the following is an oath or the statement often religious in nature taken or assented to by individual in ceremonies?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["not less than twenty thousand", "not less than fifteen thousand", "not less than twenty five thousand", "not less than fifty thousand"],
        correctAnswer: "not less than fifty thousand",
        question: "Violation of the Republic Act 8495 upon conviction be penalized by a fine of:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["receivable turn-over ratio", "acid-test ratio", "profit margin ratio", "current ratio"],
        correctAnswer: "acid-test ratio",
        question: "What is the index of short term paying ability?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["All of these", "Certified Plant Mechanic", "Professional Mechanical Engineer", "Registered Mechanical Engineer"],
        correctAnswer: "Professional Mechanical Engineer",
        question: "Which of the following is responsible in the preparation of plans, designs, investigations, valuations, technical reports, specifications, project studies or estimates and usually responsible in signing power plants more of than 3000 kW?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Sec 1", "Sec 18", "Sec 9", "Sec 4"],
        correctAnswer: "Sec 4",
        question: "Which of the following sections in R.A. 8495 is the creation of Board of Mechanical Engineering?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Feb 24, 1998", "Feb 12, 1998", "Feb 21, 1998", "Feb 14, 1998"],
        correctAnswer: "Feb 12, 1998",
        question: "Republic Act 8495 &amp;amp;quot;The Act of Regulating Mechanical Engineering Practice in the Philippines&amp;amp;quot; was approved by President Fidel V. Ramos on",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Sec 41", "Sec 21", "Sec 35", "Sec 20"],
        correctAnswer: "Sec 21",
        question: "Which of the following sections in R.A. 8495 deals on the Oath taking of the successful examinees?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Republic Act 8945", "Republict Act 8495", "Republic Act 8745", "Republic Act 7920"],
        correctAnswer: "Republict Act 8495",
        question: "Which of the following is known to be &amp;amp;quot;The Philippine Mechanical Engineering Act of 1998&amp;amp;quot;?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["corporation", "sole proprietorship", "none of these", "partnership"],
        correctAnswer: "sole proprietorship",
        question: "Which of the following is the easiest form of ownership?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Scope of Examination", "Reports of Ratings", "Reports of Ratings", "Re-examination"],
        correctAnswer: "Scope of Examination",
        question: "Which of the following is Article 3, Sec 17 of RA 8495?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["escalatory clause", "Bid Bulletin", "Technological Assessment", "Delicts"],
        correctAnswer: "Bid Bulletin",
        question: "Which of the following additional information to prospective bidders on contract documents issued prior to bidding date?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Franchise", "Patent", "Copyright", "Trademark"],
        correctAnswer: "Copyright",
        question: "What limits the unauthorized used rights obtained for books, periodicals, dramatic composition, musical compositions, works of art, etc.?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Legal Agency", "Contract", "Franchise", "Corporation"],
        correctAnswer: "Contract",
        question: "What is legally binding agreement or promise to exchange goods or services?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Natural Born Citizen and a Resident of the Philippines for at least five years.", "A professional Engineer with a valid professional license and an active practitioner of such, for 10 years only.", "A National Officer of PSME national chapter at the time of the appointment", "A past faculty member of any school offering Mechanical Engineering for a period of 5 years prior to his appointment"],
        correctAnswer: "A National Officer of PSME national chapter at the time of the appointment",
        question: "Which of the following can be a ground for disqualification to become of Member of the Board of Mechanical Engineers?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["200 HP", "300 HP", "500 HP", "150 HP"],
        correctAnswer: "300 HP",
        question: "What is the maximum capacity that a certified plant mechanic (CPM) is authorized to handle?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Sec 35", "Sec 27", "Sec 42", "Sec 28"],
        correctAnswer: "Sec 27",
        question: "Which of the following sections in R.A. 8495 that deals on the Grounds for Suspension and Revocation of Mechanical Engineering Licenses?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Vested Rights", "Engineers Right", "Special Rights", "Automatic Rights"],
        correctAnswer: "Vested Rights",
        question: "What term is used for Automatic Registration of Practicing Mechanical Engineers?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Trademark", "All of these", "Copyright", "Patent"],
        correctAnswer: "Patent",
        question: "What is obtained by the inventor or discoverer of any new and useful process, machine, manufacturer or composition of matter, or new and useful improvement?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Statement of Policy", "Rules and Regulations of the Implementation", "Title", "Statement of Policy"],
        correctAnswer: "Title",
        question: "Which of the following defines Article 1, Sec 1 of the Philippine Mechanical Engineering Act of the Philippines?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Material Breach", "Fraud", "Negligence", "Breach of Contract"],
        correctAnswer: "Negligence",
        question: "Which of the following is an action, willful or unwillful, taken without proper care or consideration for safety, resulting in damages to property or injury to persons.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Professional Mechanical Engineering", "Mechanical Engineer", "They are on the same category", "Certified Plant Mechanic"],
        correctAnswer: "Professional Mechanical Engineering",
        question: "Which of the following is the highest category in the practice of Mechanical Engineering?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["194", "494", "294", "394"],
        correctAnswer: "294",
        question: "In the transitory provision, Mechanical Plant Engineers possessing valid certificates or registration issued under Commonwealth Act No.",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["10 years", "20 years", "5 years", "15 years "],
        correctAnswer: "20 years",
        question: "A trademark registration is issued for a period of how mnay years?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Society", "Boarding", "Integration", "Unification"],
        correctAnswer: "Integration",
        question: "What term is used for the unification of all mechanical engineers including certified plant mechanic into one organization of mechanical engineers to be accredited by the Board of Mechanical Engineering and the commission without prejudice to their membership in other associations of mechanical engineers?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["8 hours", "16 hours", "12 hours", "24 hours"],
        correctAnswer: "24 hours",
        question: "The personnel required in Mechanical plant over 2000 kW; one professional mechanical engineer provided that every mechanical work, project or plant in this category operating in more than one shift every how many hours?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["50", "54", "45", "48"],
        correctAnswer: "48",
        question: "How many sections are there in Republic Act 8495?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["must be renewed every 5 years", "are considered lifetime licenses and need not to be renewed", "must be renewed every year", "must be renewed every 3 years"],
        correctAnswer: "are considered lifetime licenses and need not to be renewed",
        question: "Under the &amp;amp;quot;PRC Modernization Law&amp;amp;quot;, licenses of professionals",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Repealing Clause", "Transitory Clause", "Effectivity Clause", "Transitory Clause"],
        correctAnswer: "Effectivity Clause",
        question: "Section 48 of the Penal Concluding provision of R.A. 8495 is known to be the:",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["40 years old", "35 years old", "30 years old", "45 years old"],
        correctAnswer: "35 years old",
        question: "What is the minimum age requirement to become a member of the Board of Mechanical Engineering?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Statement of Policy", "Effectivity Clause", "Examination, Registration and Licenses", "Separability Clause"],
        correctAnswer: "Examination, Registration and Licenses",
        question: "Which of the following is the content of Article III, Sec 12 of Republic Act 8495?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["June 21, 1973", "June 22, 1973", "June 12, 1973", "June 28, 1973"],
        correctAnswer: "June 22, 1973",
        question: "When is the effectivity of the presidential decree creating the Professional Regulations Commission?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Sec 19", "Sec 18", "Sec 20", "Sec 17"],
        correctAnswer: "Sec 17",
        question: "What section in R.A. 8495 deals on the Scope of Examinations for PME, RME, and CPM?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Article V", "Article IV", "Article VI", "Article VII"],
        correctAnswer: "Article IV",
        question: "Which of the following Articles of Republic Act 8495 deals on the provision of the practice of the Mechanical Engineering profession?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["Article IV", "Article VII", "Article V", "Article VI"],
        correctAnswer: "Article V",
        question: "Which of the following Articles of the Republic Act 8495 deals on the Penalties and Concluding Provisions?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
      {
        choices: ["escalatory clause", "secondary clause", "general provision", "general provision"],
        correctAnswer: "escalatory clause",
        question: "What is the provision in the contract that indicates the possible adjustment of material cost and labor cost?",
        topic: "NA"
      }, 
]